{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Custom Desk Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62389/":{"taskOID":62389,"originalTaskOID":62389,"setID":8873,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":503093,"questionDisplayText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","shortQuestionText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4458,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Other bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Family/Living room","answerDisplayText":"Family/Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5812,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What sort of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5645,"questionDisplayText":"Expected Level of Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of craftsmanship and materials do you expect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":503093,"questionDisplayText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","shortQuestionText":"Where will this custom desk be located?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4458,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Other bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Family/Living room","answerDisplayText":"Family/Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4458,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Other bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Family/Living room","answerDisplayText":"Family/Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5812,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What sort of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5761,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches and/or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7214,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","answerDisplayText":"photos and/or magazine cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7215,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"professional drawings","answerDisplayText":"professional drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5645,"questionDisplayText":"Expected Level of Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of craftsmanship and materials do you expect?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2829,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","answerDisplayText":"Good - I want a balance between quality and price","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3886,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","answerDisplayText":"Moderate - timing and/or price are more important to me","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3005,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","answerDisplayText":"High End - I prefer the highest quality craftsmanship and materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/62389/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62389,"taskName":"Custom Desk - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Custom Desk","xmTaskDescriptor":"Custom Desk Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"desk","textMessagingName":"Custom Desk","rolloverLongDesc":"Custom desk builders","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes office desks, built-in desks, and more","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Custom Desk.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Custom Desk Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build Custom Office or Built-In Desk","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":35,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Custom Desk Construction","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Desk - Build Custom","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Custom Desk Project","urlName":"Custom-Desk-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Custom Desk Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Customized Wood Desks","searchKeywords":"desk, furniture, office","emcCategoryOid":-12035,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8873,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}